[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all <mask> which are in <unk> . Order the <unk> in descending <unk> by <mask> <mask> .",
        "masked_answer": "select * from <mask> where <mask> =<unk> order <mask> <mask> <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all <mask> whose <mask> <unk> <mask> <unk> <unk> has a <unk> <mask> <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select * from <mask> where <mask> like <unk>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all <mask> whose <mask> <unk> is <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select * from <mask> where <mask> <mask> <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "masked_question": "List the <mask> <mask> and <mask> <mask> of those <mask> who are from <unk> and their <unk> <mask> is <unk> or <unk> <mask> is <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select <mask>, <mask> from <mask> where <mask> like <unk> and (<mask> like <unk> or <mask> like <unk>);"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all the <mask> <unk> . which were booked in the <unk> <unk> . Also display the <mask> <unk> <mask> <mask> no .",
        "masked_answer": "select <mask>, <mask> from <mask> where <mask>(<mask>) <mask> <mask> and <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all the <unk> of <mask> no . <unk> which are of <unk> <mask> and the <mask> is between <unk> <mask> <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select * from <mask> where <mask> = <unk> and [<mask>] = <unk> and <mask> <mask> <mask> and <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "masked_question": "List the <mask> no . along with its <mask> no . whose <mask> is <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select <mask> + <unk> + <mask> as <mask> from <mask> where <mask> = (select max(<mask>) from <mask>); select concat(<mask> , <unk>, <mask>) as <mask> from <mask> where <mask> = (select max(<mask>) from <mask>);"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "masked_question": "Show the <unk> of <mask> <unk> as : The <mask> whose <unk> is ( <unk> ) is in ( <mask> ) and its <mask> is ( <mask> ) . <unk> : The <mask> whose is <unk> <unk> is in <unk> and its <mask> is <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select <unk> + <mask> + <unk> + <mask> + <unk> + [<mask>] from <mask>; select concat(<unk>, <mask>, <unk>, <mask>, <unk>, [<mask>]) from <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all the <mask> which have <unk> as well as <unk> <mask> <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select distinct <mask>.* from <mask> as <mask> join <mask> as <mask> on <mask>.<mask> = <mask>.<mask> join <mask> as <mask> on <mask>.<mask> = <mask>.<mask> where <mask>.<mask> = <unk> and <mask>.<mask> =<unk>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all the <mask> which have <unk> as well as <unk> <mask> <unk> but no <unk> <mask> <mask> .",
        "masked_answer": "select distinct <mask>.* from <mask> as <mask> join <mask> as <mask> on <mask>.<mask> = <mask>.<mask> and <mask>.<mask> = <unk> join <mask> as <mask> on <mask>.<mask> = <mask>.<mask> and <mask>.<mask> = <unk> left join <mask> as <mask> on <mask>.<mask> = <mask>.<mask> and <mask>.<mask> = <unk> where <mask>.<mask> <mask> <mask>;"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "masked_question": "<unk> all the <unk> which have been booked by either <mask> no . <unk> or by <mask> no . <unk> but not by <mask> no <unk> .",
        "masked_answer": "select * from <mask> where (<mask> = <mask> or <mask> = <mask>) and <mask>!= <mask>;"
    }
]